前情提要
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
他回去救艾米丽了
He went back to save Emily.
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
艾米丽有危险
Emily is in danger.
我来自未来
I'm from the future.
一周之后的未来
The future a week from now.
再过几个小时琪拉就会逮捕卢卡斯
In a few hours Kiera is going to arrest Lucas
并发现时间旅行装置的剩余部分
and recover the rest of the time travel device.
我得改变事情的走向
I need to change things a little.
这儿改改 那儿修修
A tweak here, a push there.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
把这里所有的监控器关掉
Disabling all the CCTV surveillance in this place.
翻译： 老虎娘 Hansey 闲鱼 熊猫许个愿 向往自由 雪蓝 麦兜
两个艾力克! 两个我!
Two, Alec's! Two of me!
我必须决定要留下哪一个艾力克·赛德勒
I have to determine which Alec Sadler will bring forth
才能得到你和我都想要的未来
the future that you and I both want.
2067年 温哥华
校对： 闲鱼   后期： iamazed
小心别摔了
Don't drop that.
根据GCC的命令告知你
You acknowledge by order of the GCC
根据生活债务减免和修正条例
that these items are subject to forfeiture
这些物品将被没收
under the Life Debt Relief and Rectification Statues.
是的 是的 拜托你们快点干完吧
Yes, yes just get on with it please.
鉴于你的父母都已去世
Now that both your parents are deceased
你要继续住在这里
will you be remaining in the residence
还是归还房产用于还贷?
or return at the housing for credit?
妈妈
Mom.
我们留下
We're staying.
我们一直都住在这里
We've always lived here.
随你便
Suit yourself.
公民芯片
Citizen chip.
别把所有东西都卖了
Try not to sell everything.
快弄完了吗?
Are we getting close?
有几样东西我想留着
There are a few items I'd like to hold on to.
对我很有纪念价值 你懂的
Sentimental value, you know.
滞留物要收取百分之十的手续费
Hold-backs are subject to a 10 percent fee
用于支付上门服务费
to cover the cost of the service call.
当然了
Of course they are.
怀旧对空间和能源都是一种浪费
Nostalgia's a waste of space and energy.
你看
Look.
是不是很棒啊?
Isn't it amazing?
过去的媒介
Old media.
汉娜 这些东西你从哪儿弄的?
Hannah, where did you find this?
壁橱后面
Back of the closet.
你根本不明白
You don't understand.
这东西不能留在这里
This cannot stay here.
琪拉 别这样!
Kiera don't!
不要!
Don't!
你们两个干嘛呢?
What are you two doing?
那些是违禁品
That's contraband.
煽动性的印刷品
Seditious printed material.
我都不知道这些东西还在呢
I didn't even know we still had this.
是啊 没错
Yeah, sure.
只是很有纪念意义 对不对啊?
Sentimental value only, right?
你们都有大麻烦了
You are all in a world of trouble.
超越时间线 第三季 第二集
不
No.
谁杀的我?
Who killed me?
你是哪一个?
Which one are you?
我想我跟你一个样
I guess that answers which one you are.
你背叛了我  艾力克
You betrayed me, Alec.
你利用我拿到了时间装置
You used me to get the time travel device to you.
它在哪儿?
Where is it?
我藏起来了
I hid it.
它很安全
It's safe.
另一个呢?
And the other one?
什么另一个?
What other...?
这条时间线上的那一个
The one from this time line.
死的那个我从
The one that dead me
卢卡斯那拿到的那一个
just recovered from Lucas.
你拿了吗?
Did you take it?
你回来就是为了拿这个?
Is that what you came back for?
什么? 不 当然不是!!
What? No, no!!
我才刚刚到
I just got here.
我跟这事一点关系也没有
I had nothing to do with this.
是吗? 因为这条时间线上
Really? Because in the time line
本来没有两个艾力克·赛德勒
without two Alec Saddlers
我也没有被爆头
I didn't get shot in the head.
我想知道是谁干的
I want to know who did this.
我真的不知道
I don't know.
我只是把你留在未来世界
I just left you in the future.
没错
Yes.
而现在未来回来找你算账了
And now the future is catching up with you.
你知道自己闯下多大的祸吗?
Do you have any idea the damage you've done?
琪拉 我必须要救他
Kiera I had to save her.
当时是我唯一的机会
It was my only chance.
你把一切都毁了
You've destroyed everything.
拜你所赐 我的家人可能再也不存在了
My family may never exist now thanks to you.
我知道
I know.
我知道 我真的很抱歉
I know and I'm sorry.
我当时没考虑太多
I wasn't thinking.
要是我知道你会这个下场
If I'd known you'd end up like this,
她会是...
she would end up...
你看到了吗?
You see that?
你不是唯一一个跟魔鬼做交易的人
You're not the only one who had to make a deal with the devil.
你加入他们了?
You're one of them?
自由职业者送我回来
The Freelancers sent me back
收拾你的烂摊子
to clean up your mess.
这是我能回家的唯一方法
It is the only way I'll ever get home.
你是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我必须处理掉一个艾力克·赛德勒
I have to get rid of one Alec Sadler.
很可能是你哦
It might as well be you.
市长先生!
Mr. Mayor!
是市长
Ah, it's the mayor.
瞧我怎么这么没礼貌?
Where are my manners?
我不认识你
I don't know you.
别担心我会做什么
Don't worry about me.
律师和当事人之间的保密协定
Attorney-Client privilege.
女士们 你们可以回避一下吗?
Ladies, can you um, give us a minute?
好的 那么
Okay just...
这么说你是一名律师?
So you're a lawyer?
我们有什么关系吗?
What's our connection?
说起来 你为解放组织工作
Well, you work for Liber8.
我也一样
I work for Liber8.
我叫戈登·所罗门
Gord Solomon.
律师代理人
Attorney.
声誉管理专家
Reputation Management.
麻烦解决者
Problem Solver.
我有什么麻烦有待解决吗?
Do I have a problem that needs solving?
那得看情况
Well that depends.
特拉维斯和索尼娅重归于好
Travis and Sonya are back together.
你那坐山观虎斗的小把戏
Your ploy to pit them against each other
看起来完全败露了
seems to have backfired completely
这绝对算是个麻烦 没错
so that could qualify, yes.
别紧张 我的朋友
Don't stress, my friend.
别紧张
Don't stress.
他们并不急于
They have no immediate need
对你实施血腥的报复
to exact a painful and bloody revenge.
事实上他们有计划要委托与你
In fact they have plans for you.
很大的计划哦
Big plans.
他们称为"洗白计划"
The road to legitimacy they call it.
这里面牵扯到我 市政厅
And it involves me, and City Hall
还有你权力范围的方方面面
and all the influence you can bring to bear.
多么激动人心啊!
Exciting stuff!
来吧 爽一下吧
Come on, let's do a bump.
让我们做朋友吧
Let's be friends.
做我的朋友吧
Be my friend.
那就改天吧!
Raincheck!
怎么了?
What's going on?
这是谁? 是我们认识的人吗?
What is this? Someone we know?
可以这么说
You could say that.
卡洛斯 我可以解释
Carlos, I can explain.
这是个恶劣的玩笑吗?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
我知道你接受起来会很难
I know this is a lot to take in
但我需要你的帮助
but I need your help.
什么帮助?
With what?
处理掉她
Getting rid of her.
我是说我
Me.
你本可以自己完成的
You could have done that yourself.
你想让我看到这个
You wanted me to see this.
这样更好解释一些
It makes it easier to explain.
当一个人穿越回
When someone travels back in time
已经有他存在的时间点
to a point where they have existed,
他们就会遇到另外的自己
they will run into themselves.
这就会造成麻烦
And it causes problems.
我猜他也和这脱不了干系吧?
I'm guessing he's got something to do with this?
别把我扯进来
Leave me out of this.
这里也有两个他
There are two of him as well.
都活着
Alive.
这和艾舍尔被谋杀有关系吗?
Is this something to do with Escher's murder?
等等 你说什么?
Wait, what did you say?
你知道我在说什么
You heard me.
什么时候的事?
When did this happen?
今天早些时候
Earlier today.
你都做了什么?
What did you do?
我?
Me?
你为了救艾米丽回来
You came back to save Emily,
现在艾舍尔死了我们还要面对这个麻烦
now Escher's dead and we have this little problem.
不是我做的
It wasn't me.
事情就是这样的 艾力克
That's the thing, Alec.
都是因为你
It was you.
你想改变些事情?
You wanted to change things?
结果你改变了一切
You've changed everything.
哪个才是你?
Which one are you?
哪个是去年
Which one of you is the Kiera
和我一起并肩作战的琪拉?
that I've been working with the last year?
哪个你是我的搭档?
Which one of you is my partner?
我的朋友
My friend.
卡梅伦
Cameron.
嗨 是我
Hey, it's me.
嗨
Hey.
你怎么样?
How are you doing?
网络坏了
The network is down.
和你的CMR无法连接
It's not handshaking with your CMR.
我听不见也看不到你在做什么
I can't hear or see what you're doing.
这就怪了
That's weird.
艾力克 我相信没有什么你解决不了的
I'm sure it's nothing you can't fix, Alec.
问题就在这
That's the thing.
昨天我这里突然停电了
I lost all power here yesterday.
监控全部坏掉   我所有维护用的
The CCTV system is down and all my maintenance
子程序都被另一个内部程序锁住了
subroutines are being blocked by another internal program,
我弄不明白是怎么回事
I can't figure out how or why.
另外这里很多东西都被动过了 还有些不见了
Plus a bunch of stuff is moved or missing around here.
包括那个时间旅行装置的碎片
Including the time travel slice.
你最近来过这吗?
Have you been down here?
是的
Yeah.
那碎片我拿走了
I took the slice.
我去实验室找艾米丽
I was at the lab looking for Emily.
艾米丽?
Emily?
现在不用担心
Don't worry about it too much right now
但是关于她我们俩得好好谈谈了
but you and I need to have a serious discussion about her.
好吧
Okay.
是要跟我科普一下性教育 是吗?
This isn't going to be about the birds and the bees, is it?
不是
No.
但是一样重要
But just as important.
晚点找你 好么?
I'll stop by later, okay?
没问题 拜拜
Okay, bye.
天啊
Holy shit.
找到地方了吗??
Any luck?
是啊
Yeah.
我知道一个地方可以藏尸体
I know a place that I can stash a body.
至少能藏一阵子
For a while.
直到我找出杀她的凶手
Just until I find out who killed her.
杀我的
Me.
卡洛斯我知道把这所有的
Carlos I know it's hard to reconcile
矛盾困惑都理清很难 但是信不信由你
all these contradictions, but believe it or not,
我和她一样了解你
I know you just as well as she did.
甚至是更了解
Maybe even better.
我认识的那个卡洛斯就算在
The Carlos I know stood right beside me
所有人都背弃我的时候依然支持我
when everybody else turned their backs.
你的搭档还活着
Your partner is still very much alive.
艾舍尔的谋杀有什么新进展了吗?
What's the latest on Escher's murder?
对画廊做了彻底的排查
Did a full sweep of the gallery.
目前没什么发现
So far nothing.
我们在获取目击证人的证词
We're getting eyewitness statements
还有现场监控录像
and getting CCTV footage of the area.
我想优先处理这案子
I want this made a priority.
艾舍尔是我们警局的朋友
Escher was a friend of this department.
明白
Understood.
祝贺您的胜利 当选的马丁市长
Congratulations on your victory Mayor-elect Martin.
我们警局有什么能为您效劳的?
What can the department do for you?
多谢
Thanks.
但我来不是谈政治的
But I'm not here to talk politics.
这倒挺新鲜
That's a refreshing change.
你想聊什么?
What are you here to discuss?
一笔交易
A deal.
你是解放组织的人
You're with Liber8?
我不是任何组织的人
I'm not with anyone.
他们为我的竞选出资
They contributed to my campaign
但是等我意识到他们真正的面目时
but by the time I realized who they were,
已经太晚了
it was too late.
胡扯 吉米
Bullshit Jim.
你早就知道他们是什么人
You knew exactly who you were dealing with.
我觉得我能控制他们
I thought I could handle them.
我错了
I was wrong.
现在他们想要我的命
And now they want their pound of flesh.
那你来找我们想拿什么来交换?
So you come to us in exchange for what?
我想要豁免权
I need immunity.
真的
Really.
豁免权换情报
Immunity in exchange for information.
关于解放组织的详细情报
Details regarding Liber8.
犯罪同伙 藏身之处
Associates, hideouts,
经济状况等等所有的情报
financials and intel.
那你是怎么知道这些详细信息的呢?
And how is it you know these details?
豁免权
Immunity.
也行
Maybe.
在我同意前你得让我们先尝尝甜头
You need to give us a taste before I agree to anything.
嗨
Hey.
那是什么?
What's that?
不关你事
None of your business.
琪拉 我和你是同一战线的
Kiera I'm on your side.
真的?
Really?
因为我刚刚向另一个你
Because I just covered up
隐瞒了你偷走时间旅行装置碎片的事
your theft of the time travel slice from other you.
艾力克 我来这不是给你收拾烂摊子的
I'm not here to clean up your messes, Alec.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我当时太冲动了
It was an impulse move.
另一个我现在怎样?
How is other me doing anyway?
正在努力的想弄清楚谁破坏了连接
Desperately trying to figure out who sabotaged the network link
我CMR的网络
to my CMR.
我猜那是你的杰作
I'm assuming that was your handiwork.
是的 我想如果他听到或者看到我们做的一切
Yeah I thought we'd have some awkward moments
我们之间就尴尬了
if he could hear and see everything we're up to.
有道理
Good point.
尽管我只了解你 另一个你应该用不了多久
Although knowing you,it won't take other you long
就能发现真相
to figure things out.
艾米丽怎么样?
How's Emily?
她很好
She's fine.
既然你为了救她已经惹了这么多麻烦
Don't screw up her life
就别再扰乱她的生活
now that you've gone to all this trouble to save her.
艾力克 你目前能做的最好的事
The best thing that you can do right now, Alec
就是离她远点
is leave her alone.
我想无论杀我的人是谁
I think whoever killed me
他都在找时间旅行装置
was after the time travel device.
死去的那个我刚刚从卢卡斯那拿到了碎片
Dead me had just recovered the pieces from Lucas.
你不能把实验室那边的监控录像重放一下吗?
Can't you replay the CCTV link from the lab?
我到的时候把它关了
I deactivated it when I arrived.
为什么?
Why?
我不能冒险被他看到
I couldn't risk him seeing me.
但我一直在想
But I've been thinking.
如果她的CMR连接始终处于激活状态
If her CMR link was still active
那很有可能
then there's a good chance
杀你的凶手的图像还在我...
that your killer's image is still in the buffer of my...
在他的系统缓存里
his system.
我只需要能拿到我的设备器材
I just need access to the equipment.
我能把你弄进去
I can get you in.
他在那儿吗?
Is he there?
没错
Yeah.
好吧
Alright.
怎么?你就这么大摇大摆走进去?
What? You're just going to walk in?
他不知道我不是我
He doesn't know I'm not me.
另外我和他之间有一样你和我之间没有的东西
Besides, he and I have something that you and I don't.
是什么?
What's that?
信任
Trust.
能把我们重新连上吗?
Any luck reconnecting us?
都试过了不行
On all fronts, no.
这里很多东西都不对劲 我却弄不明白
Just one of many things going on down here I can't explain.
哦 好啊
Oh, good.
你找到了
You found it.
是的
Yeah.
在一些器材下面
Under some equipment.
出什么事了?
What's going on?
没事啊
Nothing.
我在卢卡斯那找到了这些碎片
I recovered the pieces from Lucas.
放到你桌子上
I put them on your desk.
也许杰森看到了
Maybe Jason found them
想把它们放到一个安全的地方
and wanted to put them someplace safe.
那那些血怎么解释?
And the blood?
什么血?
What blood?
在我找到这些的地方有几处
A few drops where I found the slices.
我不知道
I have no idea.
琪拉 你有什么没告诉我的吗?
What are you not telling me Kiera?
没有
Nothing.
也没什么可说的
There is nothing to tell.
这是好消息
This is good news.
我离回家又更近了一步 是吗?
I'm one step closer to getting home, right?
你好好拿着
You hold onto it.
那片丢了的碎片也在你这
You still have the missing piece?
是的 我会拿给你的
Yeah, I'll get it to you.
你知道派朗在设计一个
You know Piron was working on
稳定的反物质电源
a stable anti-matter power source?
而且已经买下了罗氏能源
And bought LaRoche Energy.
但是我担心艾舍尔的研究
But I'm kind of worried that Escher's research
也会和他一起死掉
might have died along with him.
艾力克 关于艾舍尔
Alec, about Escher...
艾舍尔怎么了?
What about him?
我只是觉得
I just think that it...
一切还好吧?
Is everything okay?
我给杰森做的DNA检测
That DNA test that I did on Jason...
结果是完全匹配
it's a match.
他是我爸爸
He's my father.
这个交给我吧
I got this one.
你对普通的黑帮买卖
Regular gang business
已经没什么兴趣了 是吧 马尔科?
not interesting enough for you, Marco?
你就一定要不遗余力的变成恐怖组织
You just had to hitch your wagon to a terrorist organization.
胡说
This is bullshit.
我们不想和解放组织有丝毫的联系
We don't want anything to do with Liber8.
我又没说是解放组织
I never said anything about Liber8.
怎么?不跟我耍嘴皮了?
What? No snappy comeback?
甚至都不猜猜是谁出卖的你?
Even want to speculate who ratted you out?
好吧 让我猜猜
Well let me guess.
他刚赢得大选 他想摆平自己惹得麻烦事
He just won the election and he wants to clean up his mess.
如果你合作的话
Things would go a lot smoother for you
事情会简单多了
if you just cooperated.
不是吧 哥们
Come on, man.
市政厅已经是解放组织的囊中物了
City Hall's in the pocket of Liber8.
而你们警察和大公司合作
You guys are in bed with big business.
他妈的 我以后都分不出谁是坏蛋了
Shit, I can't even tell you who the bad guys are anymore.
特拉维斯
Travis.
我就知道你能跑出来
I knew you'd get away.
我们得谈谈
We gotta talk.
确实
We do.
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
只是全新战略的第一步
Just the first step in a whole new battle strategy.
我们走
Let's go.
杰森
Jason.
爸爸
Dad.
你知道我从来不了解我爸爸
You know I never got to know my father.
有种感觉你和我一样
Have a feeling that you and I share that.
你改变历史的计划进行的怎么样了?
So how's the changing history deal coming along?
实际上我来这就是为了这个
Actually that's why I'm here.
在另一条时间线 我和艾米丽
In the other time line I came here with Emily
利用时间旅行装置来到这里
in the time travel device.
把所有的自由职业者都吸引到这里
It brought all the freelancers.
有些枪战
There was some shooting.
她被杀死了
She was killed
就在今天
That's today.
你在等人吗?
You expecting someone?
躲起来 快躲起来
Hide hide hide hide hide hide.
嗨
Hi.
对不起这么冒失的就过来了
Sorry to just barge in like this.
这很好 没问题
No it's good, it's fine.
我只是想和你小聊两句
I just need to talk to you for a second.
哦是的是的
Oh yeah, yeah.
我明白了
I get it.
有点不顺 是吗
It's one of those days huh.
我 哦.. 我把它带来了
I, uh, I actually brought this.
哦 这东西太危险了
That's uh, dangerous.
我在你身上做了DNA检测
So I ran some DNA tests on you.
嗯哼
Mhm?
艾米丽在哪?
Where's Emily?
她马上过来
She's on her way.
哦 这可不好啊
Oh that's no good.
不好啊
That's no good.
艾米丽
Emily...
我知道你是我爸爸
I know you're my father.
你听到我说的了吗?
Did you hear me?
你没有什么想说的吗?
Are you going to say anything?
哦 我不是你的爸爸
Uh, I'm not your father.
不 你不懂
No you don't understand.
我们基因是一样的
We're genetic matches.
父亲和儿子
Father and son.
哦 该死的
Oh shit.
哦 当然了
Oh of course.
是的
Yeah.
这么说
So then...
你是我儿子?
you're my son?
也许
Maybe.
也许?
Maybe?
嘿 我收到你短信了
Hey. I got your message.
转回去
Just turn around.
什么?
What?!!
走啊
Walk.
好吧 哇喔 到底发生什么事了?
Okay, whoa, what's happening?
我在救你的命
I'm saving your life.
是吗?
Really?
真的
Really.
够了吧
Enough.
从昨天开始你就有点奇怪
You've been acting weird ever since yesterday.
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
我答应你我会把一切解释给你听
I promise I'll explain everything to you ok,
将来的某一天
one day.
给我点时间把事情弄清楚
Just give me some time to figure things out.
可以吗?
Can you do that?
是的 可以
Yeah, I can do that.
只要你需要 怎么都行
Whatever you want Alec.
好的 过来
Okay come on.
什么情况?
What is going on?
他搬进来了
Oh he's moving in.
啊 你朋友
Ah, your friend.
这个交给我吧
I'll handle this one.
你来这做什么?
What are you doing here?
做个良好市民
Being a good citizen.
当艾舍尔先生走到人生终点时
I happened to be in the general vicinity
我恰巧就在附近
when Mr. Escher met his unfortunate end.
哦 当然是了
Hm. Of course you were.
看见我活着你似乎不是很吃惊
You don't seem surprised to see me alive.
我应该吗?
Should I be?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
只是未雨绸缪
Just getting ahead of the shitstorm.
你最好确保我不会被迫
And you better make sure I don't get forced
卷入诉讼问题 逼着我说
into any legal situations where I have to say anything
一些事情
about certain things.
一些时间旅行者的事情
Certain time travelers.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
时空旅行者
Time travelers.
他们既不是保护者的朋友 也不是我们的朋友
They're no friend of the Protective, or us.
为什么你认为
What makes you think
我们不用再担心他们?
we don't have to worry about them anymore?
保护者在帮我越狱之前
Something the Protector said to me
告诉我一些事情
right before she sprung me.
他们有比我们更大的问题
They have bigger problems than us.
保护者帮你逃出来的
The Protector got you out.
是的
Yeah.
让你们俩单独待一会儿
I'll give you two a minute.
你是对的 加尔萨
You were right, Garza.
与解放组织的利益相比
Kagami was more interested in his own legacy
卡加梅更感兴趣的是自己死后所遗留下的影响
than what was best for Liber8.
我相信他是因为他是我的老师 我的导师
I believed him because he was my teacher, my mentor.
我曾经相信他的遗愿
I believed the path of resistance could be shaped
可以勾勒出我们的反抗之路 但我现在不相信了
by dead man's final wishes, and I believe differently now.
还真是凑巧啊
Convenient.
为了确保改变 我们必须直击问题的中心
To ensure change we must strike at the heart of the problem
并且绝不手软
and strike hard.
我们需要摆脱外来者
We need to rid ourselves of outsiders
重拾在未来将我们团结在一起的真理
and reconnect to the truth that united us in the future.
我们如何能做到呢?
And how exactly do we achieve that?
如果敌人不愿意和我们在战场上相见
Well, if the enemy won't meet us in the battlefield
那么我们就将战火烧到他们眼前
then we must bring the battlefield to them.
等我一下
Give me a second.
画廊的监控拍到了你的这位朋友
Your pal here was caught in the gallery's CCTV
在艾舍尔被杀前几秒还和他坐在一起
sitting with Escher, seconds before he was killed.
我也许忽略了这一段
I might have left that part out.
探长 我正准备声明一下
I'm prepared to make a statement, Detective.
是的 当时我为了一桩生意
Yes I was meeting Mr. Escher
和艾舍尔先生见了面 再没其他事情了
for a business face-to-face, nothing more.
我主动过来澄清的
I came in voluntarily.
嘿
Heh.
你觉得我该怎么办?
What do you want me to do here?
你要追查下去吗?
You want to pursue this?
随你便
Be my guest.
我没什么好隐瞒的
I have nothing to hide.
好吧
Okay.
什么事?
What's up?
没什么好事
Nothing good.
我需要你回到你的实验室
I need you back at your lab.
事实上那不是我的实验室
It's not actually my lab.
我不能说进就进
I can't just waltz in there whenever I want.
那对我极其不利
That puts me at a distinct disadvantage.
好吧 你不是秘密的
Well, you were stealthy enough
在我CMR上传的链接上安装了防火墙吗
to install the firewall in my CMR uplink.
我需要你专注于解决我的谋杀案
I need you working on solving my murder.
再说  你真的很擅长
Besides, you've always been really good at
自己照顾自己 艾力克
looking out for yourself, Alec.
你永远都不会在这件事上放过我 对吧?
You are never going to let me live this down, are you?
在这条时间线上是不可能了
Not in this time line.
我会想办法让你进实验室
I'll find a way to get you into the lab.
我需要辆车
I need a ride.
那就叫出租车吧
So call a cab.
你应该要保护我
You're supposed to be protecting me.
呃 不
Uh, no.
您想要保护 正因为如此您要待在这里
You wanted protection which is why you're camped out here.
这是两回事
That's not the same thing.
你想要安全?
You want to stay safe?
那就老实待着
Stay put.
城市商会需要和我当面谈谈
The City Board of Trade needs to speak to me in person.
你想让城里的顶级CEO们都来这?
You want the top corporate CEOs in the city to come here?
我真的不介意
I really don't care.
无论哪一种我都可以稳坐我的办公室
Either way I'm still down an office.
阁下
Your honor.
你应该关心一下
Well you should care.
据我所知
From what I understand,
你和派朗集团的关系对你来说非常重要
your relationship to the Piron Corp is very important to you.
董事会新成员等等
Being a new board member and all.
这是什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
意思是你可以推卸责任
Well it means you can point fingers
因为我和解放组织的关系
because my association with Liber8
让我实现了我的目标
has allowed me to accomplish my goals,
而你和派朗也是一样的
when you've done exactly the same thing with Piron.
你让步是因为如果你想做大事
You compromise because that's what happens
你就只能这样做
if you want to make a difference.
也许你不喜欢结果
Well maybe you don't like results.
我和你完全不一样
I am nothing like you.
继续这样告诉自己吧
Keep telling yourself that.
体育场警局需要一辆救护车
I need an ambulance at the stadium precinct.
噢 嗨
Oh hi.
那里到底发生了什么事?
What the hell happened in there?
我录完口供了
I gave my statement.
正如我所说 没有证据把我和
Like I said there's nothing connecting me
艾舍尔的死联系在一起
to Escher's killer.
至少是  没有直接的关系
Well, directly.
我知道你做了什么
I know what you did.
我做了很多事情
I do a lot of things.
你需要讲的更具体点
You'll have to be a little more specific.
你杀了他
You killed him.
你杀了艾舍尔
You killed Escher.
噢 别这样 别假装好像很伤心的样子
Oh come on, don't pretend to be all broken up about it.
好吧 那很奇怪
Okay, that was odd.
不要转移话题好吗 马修?
Can we focus, Matthew?
噢 对 抱歉
Oh yeah, sorry.
我们说到哪了
Where were we.
呃 噢 对
Uh, oh yeah.
我们在玩一场游戏 你似乎觉得
We were playing a game where you seem to think
你对一切了如指掌
you know what's going on,
而这应该对我有所影响
and that's supposed to have some kind of effect on me.
好吧 你可以省点力气
Well you can save your breath
因为无论你讲什么
because nothing you have to say
都不会让你得到你想要的
is going to get you whatever it is you want.
艾舍尔是艾力克的父亲
Escher was Alec's father.
这样啊
Huh.
我没想到会是这样
That I did not see coming.
艾力克还不知道 我也不想告诉他
Alec doesn't know yet and I don't want to tell him.
但是我想当艾力克知道你谋杀了他的父亲
But I'm guessing that your little business arrangement
你的那些生意上的计划
is going to get just a bit difficult
实施起来会有相当的难度
when Alec finds out you murdered his dad.
我懂你的意思了
I see your point.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我想要不管将发生什么
I want what's going to happen anyway.
你都离艾力克远点
Stay away from Alec.
嗯
Um.
哪一个?
Which one?
就是这样
And there it is.
琪拉 你真的想和我玩这个游戏吗?
You really want to play this game with me Kiera?
你是怎么看出来的?
How did you find out?
你刚刚告诉我的
Well you just told me.
我是个聪明人 我自己想出来的
And I'm smart, I did the math.
什么意思?
What's that mean?
当你专心的时候 一些事情就很明显
Some things are obvious when you pay attention.
并且 你知道的 也包括时间旅行
And, you know, time travel's involved.
我们能不能打开警示灯避过这些拥堵的车呢?
Can we just hit the lights and get around this mess?
我要迟到了
I'm gonna be late.
我们不能这样 先生
We can't do that sir.
十六组 在你附近有病人心跳骤停
Unit 16, cardiac arrest reported in your vicinity.
汉密尔顿街和大卫街的拐角处
The corner of Hamilton and Davie.
十六组 在路上了
16 en route.
我们马上就到
We're right around the corner.
不是吧?
Seriously?
伙计 我没时间了！
Guys, I don't have time for this!
先生 再这样我需要请您安静下来了
Sir, I'm going to have to ask you to settle down.
我们刚接到报警电话
We've received a 911 call
我们是最近的支援单位
and we're the closest support unit.
我命令你们忽略那个电话
I am ordering you to ignore that call.
这需要多久?
How long is this going to take?
噢 不会太久
Oh not long at all.
恭喜你赢得选举
Congratulations on your win.
我们为你感到骄傲
Now we're all very proud of you.
你们想干什么?
What do you want?
你在竞选中说要承担责任
Well your campaign promised accountability.
我们只是想要确认一下你会对选民们
We just want to make sure that you keep that promise
遵守这个承诺
to the voters.
我们准备了一份你的要求清单
We've prepared a list of your demands.
我的要求?
My demands?
我们的要求
Our demands.
我以为我们的要求是一致的 吉米
I thought we all wanted the same thing, Jim.
就是你会活着
You to live.
开始吧
Go.
这个城市的大型企业为了自身利益
Corporate interests in this city
从权力的中心侵蚀并滥用民主制度
have absorbed and perverted democracy at its heart.
大家选我是想让我终结腐败
Voters elected me to put an end to this corruption.
从会议室到警察局 腐败无处不在
It stretches from the boardroom to the police department.
那些大型企业披着合法经营的外衣
The pillars of legitimate business are merely fronts
吉米·马丁 坦白罪行
实则在做着大规模偷盗和勒索的勾当
for large-scale thievery and extortion.
你们知道我们看起来有多愚蠢?
Do you have any idea how stupid we look?
这个是现场直播吗?
Is this coming through live?
就在解放组织的网站上 所以任何人都能看到
It's on Liber8's website so anyone can pick it up.
艾力克来了
Alec's here.
嘿
Oh, hey.
Hey.
这孩子是谁?
What's with the kid?
狄龙警长 这是艾力克·赛德勒
Inspector Dillon, meet Alec Sadler,
我的私人技术顾问 是个天才
my personal tech, genius.
是我让他来的
I asked him to come in.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我想他能帮我们找到市长
I think he can help us locate the mayor.
那他如何能做的到呢?
And how is he going to do that?
你知道 我听的见的
I can hear you, you know.
那你就回答我的问题
Then answer the question.
我甚至都不知道我们在说些什么
I don't even know what we're talking about.
让他看看你的本事
Show him what you can do.
你在吗?
You there?
嗯
Mhm.
好的 你不能在另一个我前和我说话
Right, you can't talk to me in front of the other me.
干得不错 把他弄出去了
Nice work getting them out of here.
我正在进入你的CMR
I'm accessing your CMR.
希望我能看见是谁杀的你
Hopefully I'll be able see who killed you.
我们这可能遇到个问题
We might have a problem here.
看起来好像是很严重的视频信号干扰
Looks like some serious video interference.
该死的 居然有俩信号
Holy shit there's two signals.
你还好吗?
You okay?
DNA的事
It's that DNA thing.
看来我是给弄反了
Turns out I got it backwards.
无论怎样 艾力克我都一直支持你
Whatever it is, I'm here for you Alec.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着 我想我找到了一种方法找出
So listen I think I figured out a way to find out
杀死另外一个你的凶手
who killed the other you.
在另一个你被杀时
Looks like both Kiera's were sending video
好象两个琪拉在发射视频讯号
at the time the other you was killed.
能跟你谈谈吗?
Can I talk to you for a second?
可能需要点儿时间 但是我能去除
It may take some time but I might be able to unscramble
视频信号中的干扰
the corrupted video.
谁是凶手就一目了然了
Get a good look at your murderer.
这是你的艾力克还是我们的艾力克?
Is this is your Alec or is it our Alec?
你想说什么?
What are you getting it?
你知道虽然我能接受
You know as much as I've come to terms
什么时间旅行 超级战衣 每个人都有好几个
with all the time travel super suits multiple everybodies,
但我还是需要知道我在和谁打交道
I need to know who I'm dealing with.
这是那个我们可以信赖的艾力克吗?
Is this the Alec we can trust?
不是吧卡洛斯?
Really Carlos?
我所知道的就是这个艾力克一直
All I know is that this Alec has never given me any reason
都在帮助我们
to believe that he wouldn't come through for us.
我们会一起把这事搞定的 卡洛斯
We're all making this up as we go along, Carlos.
我们中的每个人都不可避免地会做出错误的决定
None of us are immune for making bad decisions.
不管我们来自哪条时间线
No matter what time line we're from.
这里有些背景资料
There's some background stuff here
我也许可以通过它们进入网站
I might be able to key into.
或许可以通过三角定位来锁定地点
Might be able to narrow down a location using triangulation.
这孩子蛮厉害的
Well the kid knows his stuff.
太好了 你发现什么了?
Great, what you got?
显然这个视频信号路径被完全隐藏起来
Well the video is completely masked.
辗转于无数个服务器
Bouncing off a zillion servers
所以我根本不可能追查到其原始地址
so I can't possibly track the origin,
但是有些背景声音
but there's some background noise
还有视频的干扰信号是那个地区
and video interference that may be specific
电磁波辐射所特有的
to electromagnetic radiation in the area.
还真佩服他的韧性
Gotta admire his tenacity.
够了
Enough.
什么够了?
Enough what!
什么?
What?
找到他了
Found him.
我们找到市长了
Found the mayor.
不是吧?
Really?
不可能
No way.
是的 现场直播的信号虽然被转来转去
Yeah, the live signal was being spoofed big time.
但是我启动了一个蠕虫病毒程序
But I had a worm running from months ago
是几个月前卢卡斯种植到我们的系统中的
from when Lucas planted a virus on our system.
它当时被隐藏在数字签名中
It was just buried in the digital signature.
我把它激活了然后追踪它
I activated it, and traced it back.
走运了
Lucky break.
可不是嘛
Totally.
你有地址吗
Do you have an address?
是的 我马上发给你
Yeah, I'll text it to you.
太棒了
Oh great.
干得不错啊贝蒂
Good work, Betty.
谢谢
Thank you.
没事
Thanks.
就是这儿了
This is it.
废弃的仓库
Abandoned warehouse.
当然 通常都是在废弃的仓库里
Of course, it's always an abandoned warehouse.
哦 吉米
Oh Jim.
你们中的一个应该现在一枪崩了我
One of you should probably just shoot me now.
你还在吗?
You still there?
嗯
Yup.
另一个你要回到实验室了
The other you is headed back to the lab
所以你最好快点离开
so you might want to get yourself out of there.
嗯 我会尽快重置网络
Alright, I'll reset the network asap.
我可以继续远程研究你的CMR
I can keep working on the CMR playback
找到你被谋杀的那段视频
of your murder remotely.
别担心 琪拉 我们会找到凶手的 我保证
Don't worry Kiera, we'll find your killer, I promise.
谢谢你 艾力克
Thank you, Alec.
我们今晚将把你保释出来
We'll get you out on bail tonight,
但是因为你的前科 你可能要在监狱待一段时间
but with your priors you're looking at some prison time.
坐牢没问题
I can do the stint just fine.
帮我个忙儿
Do me a favour.
乐意至极
Anything within reason.
把我和这个家伙安排在一个监区
Put me in the same cell block as this guy.
嘿吉米!
Hey Jim!
你死定了!!!
You're a dead man!!!
听懂了吗? 我是说你死定了!
You understand me? A dead man!
你能去哪儿?
Where you gonna go?
快他妈坐下
Sit your ass down.
你马上就来找你
I'll get to you as soon as I can.
这期间 你什么都别说
In the meantime, keep your mouth shut.
大律师 现在说这个可是太晚了
It's a way too late for that, counselor.
但是所有那些微不足道的腐败
But all this, penny-ante corruption
和我向那些大公司所做出的承诺
pales in comparison to
比起来就不算什么了
the promises that I was made
吉米·马丁 坦白罪行
我曾承诺与例如维科内尔
by corporations such as Vickernail,
索曼托 瓦伦塔斯的合作
Sunmanto, Vermitas
甚至派朗也想让我
and even Piron who all wanted me to...
我们应该怎么办?
So what do we do?
啥也不干
Nothing.
啥也不干?
Nothing?
不起诉
No charges.
没有人想让这家伙出庭作证
Nobody wants to put this guy on the witness stand.
影响太大了
Too much to lose.
他妈的 甚至解放组织抓了这混蛋之后
Hell, even Liber8 looked like heroes
都被人们看做是英雄了
for kidnapping this scumbag.
他完蛋了
Nah, he's done.
他刚刚把自己的政治前途毁的彻彻底底
He just committed political suicide.
如果他够聪明的
If he's smart,
就再不会在这个城市露面
he'll never show his face in this city again.
解放组织这次干得很漂亮
Liber8 played this one well.
真心的不错
Hearts and minds.
我以为我们之间两清了
I thought we were done.
我对叛逆的红发女
You know, I've always had a soft spot
总是那么情有独钟
for wayward redheads.
两部均为电影
孤女安妮
Orphan Annie.
绿山墙的安妮
Anne of Green Gables.
凯洛格 我没那么多时间
I don't have all day, Kellog.
沃巴克 孤女安妮中的角色
既然沃巴克老爹不在了
Well now that Daddy Warbucks is out of the way,
我猜你需要找个新的赞助人
I'm betting you're looking for a new sponsor.
我终于摆脱了艾舍尔的控制
I'm finally free of Escher's grip
现在你又想让我为你卖命
and now you want me to work for you.
等一下
Woah woah.
我是你的话可不会这么做
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
我认为这对你来说是双赢的好事
I really think this is a win-win for you.
你继续待在你的情人身边 而我则对你的谎言
You get to stay close to lover boy and I keep your lies,
你的真名 还有你那精彩犯罪记录守口如瓶
real name and impressive rap sheet out of circulation.
随便你
Fine.
只要你敢
Bluff called.
你想告诉他的话就去啊
You want to tell him? Go for it.
我了解艾力克 他不会介意的
I think I know Alec well enough, he'll get over it.
再见
See ya.
我赌你不敢
I'll raise you.
那你就试试
Then raise me.
艾舍尔
Escher.
放屁
Bullshit.
你要是把我扯进来 我们就都完了
You connect me to that, we both go down.
而且我们都想让他死
Besides we both wanted him dead.
你要搞清楚 千万别惹一个
What you need to realize is never mess with a girl
有暴力倾向的女人
who shows a propensity for deadly force.
你说得对 但我在想的可不是这个
That's true, but that's not what I was thinking.
我在想 你怎么这么了解艾力克
I was thinking how you know Alec well enough
知道他不会原谅你杀了他父亲的
to know that he would not get over you killing his father.
艾舍尔是...
Escher was...
没错
Mhm.
我也是刚刚才知道的
I just found out myself.
红发女 我们合作愉快
It's good to be in business with you, Red.
哇哦
Wow.
我以前都不知道你想买房子
I didn't know you were in the market.
我也不知道
Neither did I.
我当时在隔壁
I was in the neighbourhood.
我看到这个出租标志的时候就认出来了
I saw the For Lease sign and I recognized it immediately.
这就是我长大的地方
This is the home I grew up in.
我的父母 祖父母
My parents, my grandparents.
都住在这里
We all lived right here.
我在这个地方有一些痛苦的回忆
I learned some pretty hard lessons in this place.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
打电话给CPS
Calling CPS.
对 我这里查到了一些违禁物品
Yeah, I see multiple prohibited items.
我需要一组法证人员
We're going to need a forensic cataloging team in here.
搜索整个房子
Search the entire premises.
这要花多少钱?
How much is that going to cost me?
相信我 夫人
Believe me ma'am;
你现在最需要担心的可不是钱的问题
the cost is the least of your worries now.
未注册的多媒体文件 虚拟或纸质材料
Unregistered media, analog or printed materials,
以及视频和音频文件
physical video or audio media
都被定为违禁物品
is classified contraband
并且按照国内情报监督法案
and subject to seizure under Section 702
第702节的规定应予以没收
of the Domestic Intelligence Surveillance Act.
这些必须立刻上交
It must be surrendered immediately.
这是法律的规定
That's what the law says.
你记得就好
You have it memorized.
我当时就是把盒子上交给你
I was bringing that box to you.
但是我不想被记录在案
I don't want this on my record.
我打算参军
I plan to join the military.
与反对分子作战
Fight against the subversives.
是吗?
Really?
我有一张公务人员应征许可
I have a public service recruitment pass.
如果你想要的话 需要一千个生活信用值
It's um, it's worth 1000 life credits to me if you use it.
我可以通过公民芯片进行转让
I can transmit it via Citizen chip.
不会有CPS的搜查?
No CPS search?
没有
No.
而且我还可以取消你妈妈的一万元信用债务
And, I'll knock 10,000 off your mother's LifeDebt.
虽然没有清零 但是也差不多了
It won't zero it out but it'll come close.
没问题
Okay.
剩下的东西我等会儿再来收
I'll come back for the rest of this later.
夫人 你真的应该
You know ma'am, you could learn a thing or two
跟你的女儿学一学
from your daughter.
你不是真的这么想的是不是 琪拉
You don't think, Kiera.
你刚刚所做的保证
That was a commitment you just made.
他们一定会要你兑现的
They'll expect you to honor it.
我知道
I intend to.
难以置信
I can't believe you.
你这么做都是为了让我摆脱这些麻烦对不对
Tell me you did that to get me out of trouble.
不是的
I didn't.
我相信这场战争 妈妈
I believe in this war, Mom.
我想要改变这个国家
I want to make a difference.
我想我要去安慰一下汉娜
I'm gonna try to calm Hannah down.
告诉我 我可以相信你 艾力克
Prove to me that I can trust you, Alec.
告诉我 你可以把我送回
Prove to me that you're the one that can send me back
我原来所在的时间
to my time.
我不要什么时间旅行了
I'm done with time travel.
从这一刻起我也不做什么家族生意了
I'm out of the family business from this moment.
我只是想让艾米丽快乐而已
I just want to make sure Emily's happy.
我关心的就只有这件事
That's all that matters to me.
我再不停手的话
The longer I'm involved with all of this,
情况只会变得更加糟糕 不管是对你 还是对我
just the worse it's going to get for you and me.
我是说对另外一个我
The other me, that is.
重要的是你爱她
The important thing is that you love her.
她也爱你
She loves you.
只要你不把真相告诉另外一个我
As long as you don't tell the other me the truth
一切问题就解决了
then everything will work itself out.
那我要怎么回去?
What about me getting back to my family?
什么都不做的话我就能回去了吗?
Is that just going to sort itself out?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道 即使有办法能让你回去
All I know is if there is a way back for you
帮你找到办法的那个人也不会是我
then I'm not the guy to help you find it?
那会是谁?
Who is?
你知道的
You know who.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
要帮忙吗?
Want some help?
今天晚上我想一个人
Actually I think I need to be alone tonight.
明天可以吗?
Start tomorrow?
没问题
Okay.